spiralvortexplay.com 2013-06-24

# Spiral Vortex Play

**Spiral Vortex Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which SpiralVortexPlay collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the http://www.spiralvortexplay.com/ website ("Site"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by SpiralVortexPlay.

**Personal identification information**

Spiral Vortex Play may collect personal identification information from Users many of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, place an order, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, credit card information. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

**Non-personal identification information**

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the IP address and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

**How we use collected information**

SpiralVortexPlay collects and uses Users personal information for the following purposes:

\- To process transactions  
We may use the information Users provide about themselves when placing an order only to provide service to that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide the service.

\- To administer a content, promotion, survey or other Site feature  
To send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them.

\- To send periodic emails  
The email address Users provide for order processing, will only be used to send them information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, and/or other requests or questions. 

**How we protect your information**

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

Sensitive and private data exchange between the Site and its Users happens over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures.

**Sharing your personal information**

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others.

**Changes to this privacy policy**

SpiralVortexPlay has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

**Your acceptance of these terms**

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy and terms of service. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

**Contacting us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:

SIC@spiralvortexplay.com

This document was last updated on November 20, 2011
